u-free-ware.com 2016-06-16

# 

WEBSITE PRIVACY POLICY 

Last updated on February 9, 2015 

This Privacy Policy constitutes the full and final agreement between (”Us” or ”We”) and You with respect to this website, which is available at: [u-free-ware.com](http://u-free-ware.com/) (the ”Website”). Please be advised that the practices described in the Privacy Policy apply to information gathered by us, our subsidiaries, affiliates and/or contractors through provision of the Website. 

Please read the Privacy Policy carefully. The Privacy Policy informs you how we may access, collect, use and/or share the information we obtain from and about you. We are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of any website and/or software that is not owned and/or operated by us and to which the Website may link or that links to the Website. 

The Privacy Policy and the Website Terms of Use available at: [u-free-ware.com/terms-of-use](http://u-free-ware.com/?tm=terms_gen&pd=Ir5wcHCtDEvlDSFJcmc%3D&dr=1) (the ”TOS”), govern your access and use of the Website. By accessing, visiting and/or using the Website, you agree to abide by the terms and conditions of the Privacy Policy and the TOS. 

The Privacy Policy may be amended by us, from time to time, in our sole discretion, and your continual use of the Website subsequent to any changes to the Privacy Policy shall conclusively mean that you accept all such changes. When we update the Privacy Policy, we will update the effective date posted on the top of this page. 

BY ACCESSING, VISITING AND/OR USING THE WEBSITE, YOU CONSENT TO OUR USE IN ANY INFORMATION THAT YOU PROVIDE TO US OR THAT WE COLLECT FROM YOU IN ACCORDANCE WITH THE PRIVACY POLICY. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THE PRIVACY POLICY, DO NOT ACCESS, VISIT AND/OR USE THE WEBSITE. 

  1. Children's Privacy Policy (COPPA). 

The Website is not directed to children under the age of 13 and children under the age of 13 should not use the Website. We do not knowingly collect or maintain information collected online from children under the age of 13. 

  1. Information We Collect. 

    1. We and our partners may collect and store certain technical and non-personal information when you visit and/or use the Website. This information may include your IP address, the internet URL from which you access the Website, your browser type, computer operating system, the number of times you viewed an advertisement and whether you responded to a delivered advertisement. 

    2. We and our partners may use technologies such as cookies and pixels to collect and store your information. 

    3. In addition, if you contact us by mail, voice, email or any other form for transmission, we may keep a record of your correspondence, including any information contained therein and we may use it to improve the Website, our services or otherwise at our sole discretion. Your correspondence may include personal information should you chose to provide it to us. 

  2. How We Use Your Information 

    1. We may use your IP address for a number of purposes, such as, without limitation, system administration, to report aggregate information to our business partners and/or to audit the use of the Website. We may associate your IP address with the personally identifiable information you provide. 

    2. We may use your information internally to (i) enhance your experience of the Website; (ii) improve the content, layout and/or design of the Website and marketing efforts, and (iii) to determine general trends from visitors to the Website. 

    3. We may use your information to administer the Website and help diagnose technical problems. Your information may also be analyzed so that we can provide you with useful information and can serve you in the best manner possible through enhanced features and functions on the Website, including by delivering targeted content to you. 

    4. We retain information for as long as is required, allowed or we believe it useful, but we are not otherwise obligated to retain information for any period of time. Subject to applicable law, we may dispose of your information in our sole discretion without notice. 

  3. Information We Share 

    1. We do not sell, rent, trade, license or otherwise disclose your information to anyone other than to entities under our direct control, except that we may disclose your information: (i) to third parties: (a) whose services we use to perform specific business-related functions on our behalf; and (b) in response to requests from law enforcement officials conducting investigations, subpoenas, a court order, or if we are otherwise required to disclose such information by law; (ii) when we deem, in our sole discretion, that it is necessary to (a) protect our rights, property, security and/or safety or those of others; (b) enforce the TOS, the Privacy Policy or any other agreements, terms or conditions that apply to your use of the Website; or (c) in the event of an emergency; (iii) as part of a transaction in which we or any of our assets, including the Website, may be sold. Such transaction may be in the form of a change in control, merger, consolidation, restructuring, the sale of certain of our assets (including through bankruptcy), or other corporate change including, without limitation, during the course of any due diligence process; (iv) in an aggregated manner (such as the number of daily visitors to the Website); and (v) for any other purpose we may deem desirable with your consent. 

    2. We may use third party ad serving technologies to collect information as a result of ad serving through the Website. These third parties may use Cookies (as defined below) or other technologies for such purpose. We currently use Google AdWords Remarketing, which allows us to reach users who previously visited the Website, by presenting them with relevant ads. For that purpose, Google uses Cookies to serve ads based on your past visits to the Website. A ”Cookie” is a small text file saved on your computer to help store preferences and other information that is used on webpages that you visit. 

    3. We may use third parties’ services in order to analyze information and statistics collected from users of the Website. We currently use Google Analytics which uses the following sources for collecting information: (a) the HTTP request of the user; (b) browser/system information; and (c) first-party Cookies. These Cookies do not collect any personally identifiable information. 

    4. You acknowledge that we have no control over, and assume no responsibility for any third party site, services and/or content that is made available on the Website. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of these sites, software and/or content prior to providing them with any information. 

  4. Data Security 

The Website incorporates physical, electronic, and administrative procedures to safeguard the confidentiality of your personal information. We take reasonable precautions to protect your information from loss, misuse or alteration. We maintain reasonable physical, electronic and procedural safeguards for your information. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or from the Website. You use the Website at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we will use commercially reasonable efforts to ensure its security on our systems. 

We are not liable for any breach of our systems or interception of our transmission, and we hereby disclaim, to the fullest extent provided under law, any liability associated with any breach of security, data or information. 

  6. Contact Us 

If you have any questions about the Privacy Policy, contact us at [u-free-ware.com/contactus](http://u-free-ware.com/?dr=1&tm=contactus&pd=Ir5wcHCtDEvlDSFJcmc%3D)
